as long as I'd known your Uncle Barney, he'd always had some pretty strong opinions on relationships.
从我认识Barney叔叔开始 他就总对恋爱这回事有些固执的观点
Your girlfriend?
你的女朋友?
She's your girlfriend?
她是你的女朋友?
She's a girl and a friend?
她是个女的 还是个朋友?
Do not humanize the enemy,Ted.
别把敌人给人性化了 Ted
But nice to meet you.Barney Stinson.
但是很高兴见到你 Barney Stinson
And yet, in the fall of 2009, he was the one with the girlfriend.
而到了2009年的秋天 他成了有女朋友的人
Go ahead.Open it.Open it!Open it!Open it!Open it!
继续啊 打开 打开 打开...
It's my porn collection!
是我的A片集合!
Just kidding.That would be weird.
开玩笑的 那不就太怪了吗
- It's your porn collection. - It's my porn collection!
- 是你的A片集合 - 是我的A片集合!
I'm giving you my porn.
我的A片都送给你了
Now that things are so great with Robin, I don't need it anymore.
既然我跟Robin相亲相爱 我也不再需要它们了
Wow,you are voluntarily...
哇 你自愿...
giving up your porn?
送出你的A片?
You really are serious.
你们俩够认真的
- Yeah,well, that's obvious. - What does that mean?
- 是的 很明显是的 - 什么意思?
Oh,nothing, it's just,you know, you got relationship gut.
噢 没什么 就是 你已经有了"恋爱肚腩"
What?No,I do not "got relationship gut.
什么? 不 我才没有什么"恋爱肚腩"
" That is ridiculous.
可笑至极
It's no big deal.
这没什么大不了的
I mean,once you're dating someone, it's natural to let things go a little bit.
我是说 当你开始和某人恋爱 放纵体重也是情有可原的
Trust me, we've been there.
相信我 我们是过来人
Boy,did I pudge out for a while.
伙计 有一阵子我发福了很多
Well,we should get going.
好吧 我们得走了
Good-bye,my sweet, beloved friends.
再见 我最最亲耐的好朋友们
You have always been there for me.
你们总是默默地支持着我
You'll be missed.
我会想念你们的
He's talking to the porn.
他指的是A片
- Bye,Robin. - See you,Robs.
- 再见 Robin - 再见 Robs
God,look at these videos.Space Orgy?
天呐 瞧瞧这些片子 "太空狂欢会"?
Horny Co-Ed Surprise Party 23?
"饥渴放荡女的惊喜派对第23部"?
You'd think after the first 22 parties, the co-eds wouldn't be surprised anymore.
经历过之前的那22个派对 放荡女应该不会再惊喜了吧
So,uh...
所以...
we can get rid of these for you.
我们帮你把这些扔掉吧
Yeah.No.No-no-no-no-no-no.
不 不 不....
It's not a problem.
没关系的
I'll-I'll take care of them.
我...我来处理就好
Are you sure?I mean,no biggie.
你确定? 我是说 真的不麻烦的
We can just swing by the back alley and drop the box in the Dumpster.
我们可以绕道去后街把盒子扔到垃圾箱
I see six of the words you just said on this video label.
你刚才说的话中有6个单词 出现在这部A片的标题里
Seriously,it's not a big deal.I will take care of it.
我是说真的 没关系 我自己来就好
- No,'cause I,I mean... - Leave them!
- 不是 我是说...那个 - 给我放下!
You know,in a way it's sad,right?
某种程度上说 这是个杯具
I mean,Barney's giving up his porn.He's got relationship gut.
Barney放弃了A片 又有了"恋爱肚腩"
They eat at the same diner every night.
他们每晚在同一家餐厅吃饭
It-it's,like,the end of Barney Stinson as we know him.
以我们对他的了解 这简直是Barney Stinson的坟墓
- Yeah,well,so what?They're happy. - Yeah,well,we gotta go.Later.
- 是吧 那又怎么样 他们很开心 - 是的 我们也走了
- So what'd you get? - I gotSquat.
- 你拿到了什么? - 我拿到了"Squat"(Squat: 蹲式 Orz)
What are you...I thought I saw you take one.
什么...我看到你拿了一部的 (Marshall把squat理解成"什么也没有")
Yeah,I did.It's calledSquat.
是啊 我拿了 片名就叫"Squat"
ArchiSexTure.
"建筑性学"
That is not how you spell "Buckminster Fuller.
Buckminster Fuller才不是这么拼写的呢! (美国建筑学家)
" Kids,pornography is bad, and so I was getting rid of that vile pornography right away...
孩子们 色情录像危害很大 所以我马上会把那箱A片给扔了
I am getting rid of this vile pornography right away.
我马上就会把这箱A片给扔了
when something terrible happened.
突然间 可怕的事情发生了
Oh,no.
不!
WOMAN : ArchiSexTure...
建筑性学...
Hello,Ted.
你好 Ted
If you are watching this tape-- and I knew you'd pick this one--
如果你正在看这卷带子  我就知道你会挑这部的
then you are now in possession of my porn.
代表我的A片归你所有了
This can only mean one of two things: either I'm dead,
这仅有两种可能: 要么我死了
or I'm in a committed relationship.
要么我正式恋爱了
If I'm dead, I want you to honor my memory
如果是我死了 我想让你尊重我的遗愿
by taking my body to the Hamptons and recreating Weekend at Bernie's.
把我的遗体运到汉普顿 重演"Bernie家的周末" ("Bernie家的周末"专指某种性交方式)
I want to dance.
我想要跳舞
I want to have sex with a girl.
我想和一个女孩嘿咻
And I want to go fishing.
我也想去钓鱼
If,on the other hand,I'm in a committed relationship,
另一种可能  如果我正在恋爱的话
then as your best friend, I have only one request:
作为你最好的哥们 我只有一个请求
please,for the love of God, get me out of it!
求你 看在苍天的份上  把我解救出来吧
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com/=-  Proudly Presents
-=伊甸园美剧论坛 http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com/=- YTET-泡泡飞
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 小桑 花竹梗 校对: 伤心欲绝的小毛毛 时间轴: YTET-泡泡飞
How.I.Met.Your.Mother Season 05 Episode 07
老爸老妈浪漫史 第五季 第七集
I might look happy, but don't believe it.
也许我看上去很快乐  但这只是表面
Barney Stinson is meant to be single.
Barney Stinson注定是单身的
So please,if you value my best-friendship--
所以求你了 如果你在乎我们的友情
that's right,Marshall, I'm his best friend, how does that feel?
没错 Marshall 我才是他最好的朋友 伤到你的心了吗
-- then get me out of this.
那就把我从这里解救出来
And finally,since you were expecting some porn...
最后 既然你期待着看A片...
No,no,no,baby, don't worry.
不 不 不 宝贝 别担心
The flashing green light means it's off.
绿灯一闪一闪说明摄像机是关着的
Are we sure he was finished talking?
确定接下来他没有什么要说的了吗?
Look,there's no reason we should take this seriously,right?
我们没必要把事情看得那么严重
Of course not.This is an old tape.
当然不会了 这是很久以前拍的带子
Barney is happy with Robin.
Barney和Robin在一起很快乐
But over the next couple weeks, I started to notice things.
但是接下来几周 我开始注意到一些事情
Barney and Robin stopped having crazy adventures.
Barney和Robin的热度在退减
So what'd you guys do last night?
昨晚你俩干什么了?
I wanted to go to a concert.He wanted to go to a party.
我想去看演唱会 而他想去派对
Obviously,we couldn't do what just one of us wanted,
很显然 我们无法做只有其中一个人想做的事
so we just stayed in, watched a movie on cable.
所以我们就呆家里  一起看了部有线台的电影
It wasLegen-- wait for it-- ds of the Fall.
那就是 燃情...来了..岁月
Legends of the Fall!
燃情岁月!
It was okay.
一般般吧
Barney stopped being himself.
Barney不再是他自己
Hey,Barney,I'm,uh,I'm chatting up this girl over there,
Barney 我正跟那个妞聊天
and I could use a little help landing the plane.
泡到她我还需要点帮助
Sorry,Ted,I'm my own wingman tonight.
对不起 Ted 今晚我只帮自己泡妞
And Robin got annoyed at everything he said.
只要Barney一开口 Robin就很不耐烦
So,how are you two?
你俩怎么样?
- So great.Relationships are the best. - shut up.Shut up.
- 好极了 恋爱真是太棒了 - 闭嘴 闭嘴
- Shut up,shut up,shut up... - The sharing, the compromise, the monogamy--
- 闭嘴 闭嘴... - 分享 妥协 一夫一妻
- can't beat it. - Shut up,shut up...
- 令人无法抗拒 - 闭嘴 闭嘴...
Catchphrase!
都是重点词! 对
But the worse they got...
他们的关系越糟糕...
I'm full...sweetie.
我饱了 亲爱的
the more they kept saying things were great.
就越把"好极了"挂嘴边
Now,in reality, Barney and Robin only kind of let themselves go.
事实上 Barney和Robin只是放纵了一点点
But after another few weeks, to us,they seemed like this.
但是我发誓 几周后 对我们来说 他们看起来就像这样
I'll be there...
我马上过去
in a minute.
让我休息一分钟
- They're killing each other. - They love each other.
- 他们摧残对方 - 他们深爱对方
Barney and Robin love each other, but they're not Barney and Robin anymore.
Barney和Robin彼此相爱 但他们都不是自己了 他们就是一个胖男人和一个老女人
They're the fat guy My favorite '70s detective show.
就像我最爱的"70年代侦探秀"
Look,it's so clear.
太明显了
Barney's been overeating because he hates being tied down like this.
Barney暴饮暴食是因为他不喜欢被束缚
And Robin's stressing out because she hates what Barney's turned into.
Robin压力过大是因为 讨厌Barney变成这个样子
No,they're a perfect match.
不啊 他俩挺般配的
Well,maybe that's the problem.
好吧 也许那正是问题所在
Maybe they're too similar.
可能是因为他们太相像了
It must be tough having two alpha dogs in one relationship.
一段恋爱关系没有两只阿尔法犬
- We have two alpha dogs in our relationship. - Sure we do,sweetie.
- 我们的恋爱关系里就有两只阿尔法犬 - 那是当然的 亲爱的
If they're not happy, why don't they just break up?
如果他们不快乐 为什么不分手呢?
Because they're too stubborn.
因为他们太固执了
Neither one of them wants to be the first to admit that they want out.
没有一个人愿意先承认自己准备放弃
They're playing Relationship Chicken.
他们在玩"恋爱鸡汤"游戏
I think Barney ate the relationship chicken.
我倒是觉得Barney把"恋爱鸡汤"喝掉了
Ted,it's just a rough patch.
Ted 这只是个小难关而已
It takes time getting used to being with someone else.
需要花些时间去习惯和某人相处
And they're both...
他们都很...
- What's the nice word for selfish? - Independent.
- "自私"的褒义词是什么? - 独立
Independent.Every relationship goes through this.
很独立 每段感情都会经历这些
It's true,um, I have this astronaut friend-- totally loved his fianc?e.
这是真的 我有个宇航员朋友 他很爱他的未婚妻
And then,the day before his mission she caught him with,like,
然后 在他执行航空任务前 她发现他...
four other chicks, a couple of dudes.
和四个女的 还有两个男人在一起
Things got really tense.
形势就变得很紧张了
Um,finally,she ended up sneaking onto the space shuttle...
最后 她偷偷溜进航天飞船里...
- Are you talking aboutSpace Orgy? - Yes,I am.
- 你是在说"太空狂欢会"吗? - 是的 没错
Ted,it's just a rough patch.Just let things run their course.
Ted 这只不过是个小难关而已 顺其自然吧
- She's right. - But...
- 她说的没错 - 但是...
Two-to-one,Ted.Leave them alone.
二对一 Ted 别去管他们
So I did leave them alone.
所以我真的没去管他们
But that weekend...
但在周末...
Have you noticed how beef ribs used to always be disgusting,
你知道牛排骨以前有那么恶心
and then recently, they found a way to make them really delicious instead?
但是最近 他们想到法子把它们做得很美味
Okay,Barney,I'm going to go ahead and ask you this head-on.
好吧 Barney  我必须要问你个问题
Are you happy with Robin?
和Robin在一起你开心吗?
Are you kidding?How could I not be happy with Robin?It's Robin!
你开玩笑吧 怎么会不开心呢 她可是Robin啊
So are you happy?
所以你觉得开心咯?
I can't believe you would even ask me that.
我无法相信你竟会问我这个
I mean,yes, we fight all the time, but you know what they say about relationships:
我是说 对 我在挣扎 但是你知道 大家是怎么说恋爱关系的吗
Every moment's a battle.
每时每刻都像一场战争
So are you happy?
所以你觉得开心咯?
And you know what goes hand in hand with fighting?
你知道可以和争吵相抗衡的是什么吗?
The makeup sex.
"讲和性爱"
Which is different when you're in a loving, long-term relationship.
在一段付出真情的长期恋爱关系里就不同了
Heads we have sex, CB tails we order a whole pizza and just lay here moaning.
正面我们就做爱 反面我们就叫一份披萨 躺着吃 发出享受的声音
Ah,great.Let the coin decide.
好吧 让硬币来决定
- Which was pizza again? - Tails.
- 哪面是披萨? - 反面
It was tails.
是反面
Sex-- am I right?
做爱 我说的对吗
Thank God that's mostly over.
谢天谢地马上就吃完了
I'm still hungry.You hungry?
我还是饿  你饿吗
We have to break them up.
我们必须把他们拆散
You're right.Barney and Robin are miserable together, but they're too stubborn to admit it.
你是对的 Barney和Robin在一起就是个大杯具 但是他们太顽固了 无法意识到这点
So we have to get them to break up.
所以我们要想办法让他们分手
How do we do that?
我们该怎么做?
We unleash...
该是...
the Kraken.
北海巨妖出场的时候了...
Kids,as you know, earlier that year I'd learned that Lily had broken up not one,
孩子们 你们知道的 早些时候 我发现Lily拆散了我和不只一个
not two,but seven of my past relationships.
不只两个 而是7个前女友的恋爱关系
Forget it.I'm retired.I'm out of the game.
忘了它吧 我金盆洗手了 早就不玩那游戏了
But nobody's better than you.
但是没人能玩得过你
I'm telling you, I swore off that racket.
我告诉你 我下决心不再骗人了
I've gone legit.I'm a matchmaker now.
我从良了 我现在是个媒人
Set me up with someone.
帮我介绍一个吧
Whoa,I'm just starting out.
喂 我是新手好吗
Please.You've,you've got to break them up.This relationship is killing them.
求你了 你必须拆散他俩 再在一起会害死他们的
I know it is, but I've learned my lesson.
我知道 但是我已经学到教训了
No more interfering.Let things run their course.
不做干预 顺其自然
- It's two-to-one. - Yes,but the one is me.
- 二个对一个啊 - 但是我是那"一个"
All right,we don't need her.We can break them up on our own.
好吧 我们不需要她帮忙 我们自己就能让他们分手
How?
怎么做?
Okay,remember when Robin and I were dating?What was the one big thing that really freaked her out?
好吧 记得Robin和我约会那会吗  最让她害怕的事情是什么
No,no,no,no,no-- Ted,you cannot do this to me!
不 不...Ted 你不能这么对我
No-no-no!
不 不 不!
- What are you talking about? - This!
- 你在说什么? - 这个!
This is what I'm talking about.What is this doing in my champagne?
这就是我说的  这东西为什么在我的香槟里?
If we make Robin think for even a second that Barney is proposing, she'll lose it and they'll break up.
如果我们让Robin认为 哪怕一秒钟  Barney要求婚 她就会抓狂 他们就会分手
That's crazy.Why don't we just, uh,like,lead Barney into temptation?
很疯狂 为什么我们就不能诱惑Barney呢?
We'll find some hot woman to hit on him...
我们找个辣妹来勾引他
Okay,the ring thing.
好吧 还是用戒指那个主意吧
Stakeout van.
监视车
- What? - We should've gotten a stakeout van.
- 什么? - 我们需要一辆监视车
We could've ordered pizza, looked through big binoculars and said,
我们可以订份披萨 透过大望远镜 然后说
"This ain't what I signed up for," stuff like that.
"这可不是我预料中的" 那样的话
Shh,here comes the waiter.
嘘 服务员过来了
Please shut up.
闭嘴
What?
啥?
Oh,I thought you said something,sorry.
我以为你讲话了 抱歉
Is that an engagement ring?
这是订婚戒指吗?
- Are you... - Oh,no.No.That is not me.
- 你... - 不 不 不是我
They must have delivered it to the wrong table.
肯定是他们拿错了
Can you imagine us getting married?
你能想象我俩结婚吗?
Well,we are committed to each other.
我们都忠于对方
Most of your stuff is already at my apartment.
你大部分东西都在我公寓里
It might make taxes easier.
没准缴税能方便点
It'd speed up your citizenship.
能让你更快地入籍
"Scherbatsky" is so hard to spell.
"Scherbatsky"好难拼
My mom would be so happy.
我妈会乐开花
- Yeah,I guess so. - Yeah,no reason not to.
- 嗯 好吧 - 嗯 没理由不结婚
- We're getting married! - Not so loud,geez.
- 我们要结婚啦! - 别那么大声 天哪
What did you do?I am furious right now!This is so wrong!
你们干了什么好事? 我快气爆了! 太离谱了!
Lily,will you be my maid of honor?
Lily 你愿意当我伴娘吗?
Oh,my God!I would love to!
我的天! 愿意得不了!
Are you out of your mind?
你们哪根筋不对?
You knew they were playing Relationship Chicken, and what did you do?
你们明知道他俩互相扛着 你们都干了啥?
You put an engagement ring in front of them!
在他们跟前放了个订婚戒指!
Okay,that's it.I'm taking over.
好吧 我接手了
Coming out of retirement for one,last breakup.
重出江湖拆散最后一对
All right.How are we going to do it?
好的 我们要咋做?
These guys are in so deep, just one fight ain't going to do it.
他们泥足深陷 光凭一次小打小闹没啥用
We need to reignite the four biggest fights they've ever been in all at once.
我们得一下子引爆他们 吵得最猛的四次架
Number one: The Battle of the Dirty Dishes.
一号:脏盘子之战
Number two: The Ex-Girlfriend Conflict.
二号:前女友之争
Don't you know that girl over there?
那边的妞你不认识?
No,I don't think so.
嗯 我想不认识吧
No,in fact, I have definitely not-- oh,hey,it's Meg.
其实 是绝对不  嘿 那是Meg
Wow,I am certainly not comparing you two in my mind right now.
哇 我现在脑子里可没把你俩作对比
Hey,will you get that for me?
嘿 能帮我捡下吗?
- Please?I'm not... - really？What's the problem?
- 好吗? 我不... - 是吗? 你搞什么?
- Why do you keep-- you're embarrassing me in public. - You're constantly putting me in these positions.
为啥你老是在众目睽睽之下要我难堪? 一而再 再而三地让我丢脸
Oh,my God...
我的天
Number three: TheStar WarsAltercation.
三号:星球大战之辩
Isn't it time you got rid of your stupid doll?
咋还不把这傻不啦叽的娃娃丢掉?
It's not a doll.It's a stormtrooper.
这不是娃娃 是冲锋兵
Uh,he's wearing a diaper.
还穿尿布
It's not a diaper,Robin, it's protective armor.
这不是尿布 Robin 是防护铠甲
Stormtrooper?More like storm-pooper.
冲锋兵? 更象是冲锋屁眼
Stop it.
别闹了
Oh,it sounds like your storm-pooper here needs a changing.
貌似你的冲锋屁眼要换尿布啦
Okay,you know what?I'm sick of it.
好吧 烦透了
- What?I'm sick of the jokes--  - I didn't say anything.
- 这种笑话恶心死了 - 啥? 我啥也没说
- the joke about the magic, the joke about the stormtrooper... - I can't...I can't joke?
- 拿魔术 拿冲锋兵开涮 - 我不能...我不能开玩笑了?
And of course the biggie: The Canadian/American War.
当然还有最劲爆的:美国加拿大大战
Thank God that song's over.
谢天谢地那歌终于完了
Who the hell was that old lady singing?
那唱歌的老女人到底是谁?
Okay,you know that Neil Young is my favorite musician.
好吧 Neil Yong是我最喜欢的音乐家 这点你心知肚明
Right.Now,was that the same old lady who played Archie Bunker's wife inAll in the Family,
对 "全家福"里扮演 Archie Bunker老婆的也是这老女人吧?
or just a sound-alike?
还只是声音象?
Neil Young is a Canadian treasure.
Neil Young是加拿大的瑰宝
Do not make fun of Neil Young.
别拿Neil Young开涮
Robin,I would never make fun of a defenseless old lady with vocal cord paralysis...
Robin 我从不取笑手无缚鸡之力 又声带麻痹的老妇人
- ever. - Oh,here we go.In public?
- 从不 - 又来了 众目睽睽之下?
- Yeah,in public.I'll go there.What's the problem? - Really?Everything I say...
- 嗯 就是众目睽睽 那又怎样? - 是吗? 我所说的一切...
I got it.
明白
We e-mail them pictures reminding them of each of these fights.
我们把这些勾起怒火的照片 发到他们邮箱
You child.Here's how it goes down.
真幼稚 应该这样
They're at the diner...
他们吃饭的时候...
LILY: First,rekindling the Canadian-American debate, Ontario native Alan Thicke stops by the table.
首先 引爆美国加拿大大战 让安大略省的Alan Thicke前去搭讪 (成长的烦恼里的老爸)
Alan Thicke?
Oh,right.Robin knew him back when she was a singer.
对 Robin当歌手那会就认识他
Yeah,and they still keep in touch.I already got his number off her phone.
嗯 他们还有联系 我已经 从她手机里弄到他号码了
Seriously...amateurs.
说真的...只是爱好而已
LILY: So Alan Thicke restarts the Canada-U.S.fight.
由Alan Thicke重燃加美之斗的战火
Right at that moment, Crazy Meg shows up.
就在那时 疯Meg登场
Then,a stormtrooper happens to walk by the window.
然后 冲锋兵恰好路过窗口
And just when they can't take anything more, a busboy walks by with a tray full of what?
就在他们快要崩溃时  打杂工经过 手上托着满满的
Dirty dishes.
脏盘子
Lily.This is your masterpiece.
Lily 这真是你的旷世杰作
We're getting a stakeout van!
我们要辆监视车!
A station wagon?Really?
旅行车? 开啥玩笑?
You rented a station wagon?
你借了辆旅行车?
Yeah,a van cost, like,25 bucks more.
嗯 监视车要贵25多块
A station wagon?
旅行车?
Greetings,Will Robinson!
你们好 Will Robinson!
Where's the birthday boy or girl?
小寿星在哪?
Hey,climb on in.
嘿 快进来
What the hell is this?
这是啥玩意?
Oh,they didn't have any stormtroopers, so I had to get a different robot; this'll still work.
他们没冲锋兵 我只好拿别的机器人将就下  这个也行的
Different robot?Stormtroopers aren't robots.
别的机器人? 冲锋兵不是机器人
Of course they're robots!"Must kill Luke Skywalker.
当然是机器人! 一定干掉天行者路克
- Um,nobody says that inStar Warsat all,ever. - That's a really lousy robot voice,honey.
- 星球大战里从来就没人说过 - 好烂的机器人调调 亲爱的
Someone order an extra large sausage?
有人要超大的香肠吗?
Hey,one of Barney's videos starts off just like that.
嘿 有盒Barney录影带就是这样的开头
Hey,guys,Barney's ordering...
嘿 伙计们 Barney点了
five of something.
5样东西
I don't know if it's gonna fit in here.
我没妨碍到你们吧
- Okay,now you're just quoting the video. - Still ordering.
- 好吧 你现在是在抄台词了 - 还在点
Waiter's taking out a second pad.
服务员又拿了一本记录簿
Yeah,okay,well, we need it in here.We're on a stakeout.
嗯 好吧 我们需要你在这里 我们在执行监视任务
Shouldn't you be in a van?
不该是在监视车里吗?
- Thank you! - A van cost more.
- 谢谢! - 监视车比较贵
Score me a slice, Will Robinson!
奖励我一片香肠  Will Robinson!
No,no-no-no!You get a stain on that costume, they're gonna charge us.
不行不行! 要是弄脏服装 他们会要我们赔
Dude,will you just chill about money?
哥们 你咋那么铁公鸡?
Yeah,let the stormtrooper have a slice.
就是 给冲锋兵吃片吧
BOTH: It's not a stormtrooper!
他不是冲锋兵!
Hi,Lily?Sorry I'm late.I was looking for a van.
嗨 Lily? 抱歉 我迟到了 我在找监视车
- Thank you!So should I go say hi to Robin? - $25!
- 真要谢谢你! - 我该过去给Robin打个招呼? - 要贵25块呢!
Oh,not yet; get in the car.
还不是时候 先上车
Okay,so wait, wait,wait.
等下 等下
When they blew up the Death Star, knowing full well there were thousands of stormtroopers on it, those were people?
他们炸掉死亡之星时 明知道那里的 数千冲锋兵都是人类?
It was called the Death Star,baby.They knew what they were getting into.
那叫死亡之星 他们知道会自己的下场
Look,I don't want to play the "I'm Alan Thicke" card,
听着 我不想跑上去说"我是Alan Thicke"
but I really do have a dinner to get to,so...
但我的确要去赴场饭局 那...
Someone has got to take this sausage!
得有人包下这香肠!
Okay,were you in that video?
好吧 那录影带里的是你吧?
Were you the guy with the farmer tan?
你是那农民肤色的家伙吗?
Jonesin' for some 'za, Will Robinson!
好想吃披萨! Will Robinson!
Come on,I'm Alan Thicke!
拜托 我可是Alan Thicke!
This ain't what I signed up for.
这不是我所预期的
- That's what... - Hey,you know what?Everyone,stop!
- 那是... - 大家都闭嘴
Alan Thicke,shut up!Marshall, it's a station wagon.Get over it!
Alan Thicke 闭嘴! Marshall 就是辆旅行车 面对现实吧!
Ted,stop talking about porn!
Ted 别说黄碟了!
And for the love of God, somebody get the stormtrooper some pizza!
还有看在上帝的份上 给冲锋兵来点披萨吧!
- TED & MARSHALL: It's not a stormtrooper! - Crap!
- 他不是冲锋兵! - 完了!
They see us!
他们看见我们了!
Danger!
危险!
: Are you sure they saw us?
你确定被他们看见了?
Can I go talk to Barney now?I'm so excited!
我能上去和Barney谈了吗? 我好激动!
Do you really think he's going to propose to me?
你真觉得他会向我求婚?
Oh,honey...
亲爱的...
Forget it,Crazy Meg, we've been made.If we try anything now, they're going to know it's us.
算了吧 疯Meg 我们暴露了 要是现在 轻举妄动 他们就知道是我们搞的鬼了
I,I think we should all just go home...
我觉得我们该各回各家
This is my masterpiece.
这是我的旷世杰作
So what if they saw us?It'll still work.
被他们看见又咋样? 照样行的
Stop it.We'll think of something else.
停手吧 我们另谋他策
Let me repeat: "I am Alan Thicke.
让我重复遍:我是Alan Thicke
" : You're Alan Thicke?
你是Alan Thicke?
No.
不是
Alan Thicke,you're up.
Alan Thicke 你起来
Get on out there.
上场了
NARRATOR: And so,Lily followed through with her plan.
就这样 Lily按原计划行动
First,Alan Thicke.
首先是Alan Thicke
Followed by Crazy Meg.
接着疯Meg
Then,the robot.
然后机器人
And finally,the dirty dishes.
最后脏盘子
But by the end of it...
但最后...
LILY: They're kissing?They shouldn't be kissing!
他们啵了? 不该打啵的!
Why isn't this working?
为啥没用?
Because they're in love.
因为他们彼此相爱
It really was just a rough patch.
果真只是些小插曲而已
What the hell am I doing?
我究竟在搞啥?
This whole thing was a mistake.
整个计划都大错特错
So,uh, any of you dudes want to get high?
你们谁要点摇头丸吗?
I never thought I'd be saying this tonight,but...
我从没料想过今晚会说这些话
to Barney and Robin, the happy couple.
为Barney和Robin这对幸福的恋人干杯
That was the moment we learned that relationships take hard work,
那时我们才明白爱情会历经波折
but eventually, everything will work out.
但最后 守得云开见月明
Where's Barney?
Barney在哪?
Uh,we broke up.
我们分手了
And that was the moment we unlearned that other lesson we had just learned a few seconds earlier.
就在那时我们推翻了先前明白的道理
You see,earlier that night, when Lily thought Barney and Robin had spotted her,
那晚早些时候 Lily以为Barney和Robin发现她时
this is what they really saw.
这才是他们真正看见的
Why do that fat guy and old lady keep sta...
为啥那肥仔和那老女人老盯...
Oh,my God.That's us!
我的天 是我们
Look at us.
瞧瞧我们
Did we always look this awful?
我们一直看上去这么糟吗?
Robin,I'm not happy.
Robin 我不快乐
I mean, I wish I was.Nothing would make me happier than being happy,but...
我是说 我希望我快乐 乐得飞上云霄 可...
I'm not.
我不是
What are we doing wrong?We love each other.
我们做错了什么? 我们深爱彼此
I mean,if this doesn't work, what will?
我是说 要是这都不行 那什么能行?
- We're so similar. - We both like scotch.
- 我们过于相似 - 我们都喜欢威士忌
We're both awesome.
我们都很棒
You know,maybe that's it.Maybe there's just too much awesome here.
或许症结就在这里  没准我们棒得过头了
Exactly.
正是
Two awesomes cancel each other out, and I'm tired of being cancelled out.
两人都超棒就互相抵消了 我都厌倦这样消磨下去了
Me,too.
我也是
Are we breaking up?
我们这是在分手吗? (不要啊 群众希望你们在一起)
I think so.
我想是的
Ah,crap.
我靠
Now comes the next part.
那就进入下一阶段
The part where you and I can't go back to being friends.
我俩做不回朋友了
Well,maybe this isn't a breakup.
或许这不是分手
Maybe this is two friends getting back together.
只是两个好朋友重回到一起
ALAN THICKE: Robin!
Robin!
Oh,it's always so great to see a fellow hoser.
看见老同事真好
- Oh,it's true. - MEG: Barney!Good news!
- 的确 - Barney! 好消息!
I forgive you for the whole restraing order thing.
我原谅你发限制令的事了
Uh,hi.
嗨
- Whoa,is that a stormtrooper? - That's not a stormtr...
- 哇 那是冲锋兵? - 那是不冲锋...
You want to get out of here?
你想闪了吗?
See you guys.
再见 各位
See you,Alan.
再见 Alan
So you still on 73rd Street?
你还住在73街吧?
How do you know that?
你咋知道的?
Getting back together as friends...I like that.
重新做回朋友...我喜欢
One more for the road?
来个告别之吻?
And,I mean,who knows?Maybe,when, like,you turn 40, if you haven't found anyone...
谁说得准呢? 没准你40岁时还孤家寡人 我们就...
Oh,I already have that deal with Ted.
我已经和Ted约好了
Oh,right.Stupid.
好吧 真蠢
Well,maybe when you turn 39, if you haven't found anyone...
要是你39岁时还孤家寡人
It turns out that they really did just need to let things run their course.
结果他们要做的只是让一切顺其自然
So,uh,how's Barney doing?
那Barney咋样?
He's okay,I think.
我想他没事
It might be awhile before he fully recovers,but...
痊愈的话可能得要一段时间 但...
Did you guys just feel a chill?
你们觉得冷不?
Daddy's home.
老爹回家啦 (好帅的小Barney!!)
Robin 真高兴我们能重逢
嗯 希望很快又能见到你
真高兴你们做完那音乐录影后 还是朋友
音乐? 那个San Casol的录影
对 对 那个也是我们一起做的
"也"是啥意思?
没落了的加拿大综艺节目  真丢脸死了
猜猜会发生啥 当每个人都把手放在...
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com/=-  Proudly Presents
-=伊甸园美剧论坛 http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
YTET-泡泡飞
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 小桑 花竹梗 校对: 伤心欲绝的小毛毛 时间轴: YTET-泡泡飞
How.I.Met.Your.Mother Season 05 Episode 07
老爸老妈浪漫史 第五季 第七集